citygrounds.com 2019-07-07

# Privacy Policy | City Grounds

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

### What Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. The following types of information may be collected at this website (if you volunteer it):

  1. E-mail Address
  2. First and Last Name
  3. Billing and Shipping Address including Country, State, City & Zip Code
  4. Pertinent information specific to an event or activity.

### More About E-Mail & Postal Addresses

If you supply us with your email and/or postal addresses, and do not specify otherwise, you may receive periodic messages from us with information on new products, services or upcoming events.

If, later, you decide you no longer wish to receive such messages, every email we send out contains an "unsubscribe" link. Simply click this link and you will be unsubscribed. You may also let us know by sending an email to info@citygrounds.com. To ensure we correctly identify you (many names are similar), please be sure to include your complete name and address and all email addresses that may be associated with your record. This helps us accurately locate your information in our file. Such information will only be used to comply with your request.

If you would like to see your contact information we have on file, please stop by one of our retail locations or send an email to the address above.

### Cookie / Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

### Periodic Updates

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted. Please check this page for periodic updates on our policies regarding any personal information you've provided to us via our website. Thank you for visiting us online. We appreciate the opportunity to serve you.
